Guide to the Stanford University Technical Reports
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University technical reports
1956-1970
SC0695
Stanford University
200 Linear feet
Archival copies of technical reports resulting from sponsored research at Stanford.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research.
Description of the Collection
Archival copies of technical reports resulting from sponsored research at Stanford.
Access Terms
Stanford University; Research--California--Stanford University.; Technical literature.; Technical reports.
Collection Contents
- SA Numbers, Series 1
  - 5-SA-0001 through 5-SA-0065 (Box 1)
  - 5-SA-0066 through 5-SA-0115 (Box 2)
  - 5-SA-0116 through 5-SA-0175 (Box 3)
  - 5-SA-0241 through 5-SA-0240 (Box 4)
  - 5-SA-0241 through 5-SA-0295 (Box 5)
  - 5-SA-0296 through 5-SA-0345 (Box 6)
  - 5-SA-0346 through 5-SA-0405 (Box 7)
  - 5-SA-0406 through 5-SA-0460 [missing 0457] (Box 8)
  - 5-SA-0461 through 5-SA-0500 (Box 9)
  - 5-SA-0501 through 5-SA-0535 (Box 10)
  - 5-SA-0536 through 5-SA-0585 (Box 11)
  - 5-SA-0586 through 5-SA-0630 (Box 12)
  - 5-SA-0631 through 5-SA-0685 (Box 13)
  - 5-SA-0686 through 5-SA-0740 (Box 14)
  - 5-SA-0741 through 5-SA-0795 (Box 15)
  - 5-SA-0796 through 5-SA-0850 (Box 16)
  - 5-SA-0851 through 5-SA-0905 [missing 0871] (Box 17)
  - 5-SA-0906 through 5-SA-0940 (Box 18)
  - 5-SA-0941 through 5-SA-1000 (Box 19)
  - 5-SA-1001 through 5-SA-1060 [missing 1007] (Box 20)
  - 5-SA-1062 through 5-SA-1105 (Box 21)
  - 5-SA-1106 through 5-SA-1150 [missing 1148] (Box 22)
  - 5-SA-1151 through 5-SA-1185 (Box 23)
  - 5-SA-1186 through 5-SA-1225 (Box 24)
  - 5-SA-1226 through 5-SA-1280 (Box 25)
  - 5-SA-1281 through 5-SA-1335 (Box 26)
  - 5-SA-1336 through 5-SA-1395 (Box 27)
  - 5-SA-1396 through 5-SA-1401 and 6-SA-001 through 6-SA-0055 [missing 6-SA-0028 through 0044] (Box 28)
  - 6-SA-0056 through 6-SA-0100 [missing 0100] (Box 29)
  - 6-SA-0101 through 6-SA-0175 [missing 0101 – 0117, 0120; 0132 – 0135; 0154 – 0169; 0174; 0175] (Box 30)
  - 6-SA-0176 through 6-SA-0235 [missing 0176-0177] (Box 31)
  - 6-SA-0236 through 6-SA-0295 [missing 0251, 0253, 0268, 0271, 0277, 0292] (Box 32)
  - 6-SA-0296 through 6-SA-0335 (Box 33)
  - 6-SA-336 through 6-SA-0405 (Box 34)
  - 6-SA-0406 through 6-SA-0465 (Box 35)
  - 6-SA-0466 through 6-SA-0505 [missing 0476, 0503] (Box 36)
  - 6-SA-0506 through 6-SA-0563 [missing 0506, 0513, 0529, 0549, 0551] (Box 37)
  - 7-SA-0001 through 7-SA-0035 [missing 0034, 0035] (Box 38)
  - 7-SA-0036 through 7-SA-0085 [missing 0039, 0046, 0047] (Box 39)
  - 7-SA-0086 through 7-SA-0130 (Box 40)
  - 7-SA-0131 through 7-SA-0185 [missing 0167] (Box 41)
  - 7-SA-0186 through 7-SA-0235 [missing 0199, 0215, 0233] (Box 42)
  - 7-SA-0236 through 7-SA-0280 [missing 0254] (Box 43)
  - 7-SA-0281 through 7-SA-0335 [missing 0289] (Box 44)
  - 7-SA-0336 through 7-SA-0425 [missing 0338, 0343, 0363-0367, 0369, 0370, 0384-0401, 0403-0417] (Box 45)
  - 7-SA-0426 through 7-SA-0465 (Box 46)
  - 7-SA-0466 through 7-SA-0472; and 8-SA-001 through 8-SA-0030 [missing 0028] (Box 47)
  - 8-SA-0031 through 8-SA-0080 (Box 48)
  - 8-SA-0081 through 8-SA-0130 [missing 0083, 0118, 0120] (Box 49)
  - 8-SA-0131 through 8-SA-0180 (Box 50)
  - 8-SA-0181 through 8-SA-0245 [missing 0218, 0221] (Box 51)
  - 8-SA-0246 through 8-SA-0285 [missing 0254, 0255] (Box 52)
  - 8-SA-0286 through 8-SA-0325 (Box 53)
  - 8-SA-0326 through 8-SA-0385 [missing 0348-0351, 0363, 0365] (Box 54)
  - 8-SA-0386 through 8-SA-0430 [missing 0412] (Box 55)
  - 8-SA-0431 through 8-SA-0490 [missing 0441, 0442, 0445, 0451, 0452, 0468-0471] (Box 56)
  - 8-SA-0491 through 8-SA-0535 (Box 57)
  - 8-SA-0536 through 8-SA-0600 [missing 0544-0546] (Box 58)
  - 8-SA-0601 through 8-SA-0645 (Box 59)
  - 8-SA-0646 through 8-SA-0740 [missing 0666] (Box 60)
  - 8-SA-0741 through 8-SA-0820 [missing 0782, 0790, 0795, 0815-0819] (Box 61)
  - 8-SA-0821 through 8-SA-0865 [missing 0849] (Box 62)
  - 8-SA-0866 through 8-SA-0960 [missing 0935] (Box 63)
  - 8-SA-0961 through 8-SA-1020 [missing 0986, 1015, 1016, 1019] (Box 64)
  - 8-SA-1021 through 8-SA-1075 [missing 1023, 1032, 1057, 1058, 1061] (Box 65)
  - 8-SA-1076 through 8-SA-1143 [missing 1098-1100, 1105, 1108-1110, 1118, 1121, 1122, 1124] (Box 66)
  - 9-SA-0001 through 9-SA-0060 [missing 0005] (Box 67)
  - 9-SA-0061 through 9-SA-0120 [missing 0082, 0084, 0086, 0088, 0092, 0094, 0095] (Box 68)
  - 9-SA-0121 through 9-SA-0235 [missing 0124-0128, 0130-0139, 0141-0158, 0163, 0170, 0174, 0189-0198, 0200-0204, 0222, 0228, 0233, 0234] (Box 69)
  - 9-SA-0236 through 9-SA-0310 [missing 0237-0239, 0291, 0297, 0298] (Box 70)
  - 9-SA-0311 through 9-SA-0380 [missing 0312] (Box 71)
  - 9-SA-0381 through 9-SA-0425 [missing 0406] (Box 72)
  - 9-SA-0426 through 9-SA-0485 [missing 0430] (Box 73)
  - 9-SA-0486 through 9-SA-0580 [missing 0509, 0519, 0520, 0523, 0528, 0529, 0536, 0538-0540, 0543, 0569-0575, 0577-0579] (Box 74)
  - 9-SA-0581 through 9-SA-0666 [missing 0581, 0582, 0584, 0585, 0587, 0595, 0603, 0605, 0610, 0611, 0614, 0616, 0622-0626] (Box 75)
  - 70-SA-0001 through 70-SA-0075 [missing 0069] (Box 76)
  - 70-SA-0076 through 70-SA-0135 [missing 0099, 0101, 0107, 0111, 0118, 0121, 0122, 0124, 0127, 0135] (Box 77)
  - 70-SA-0136 through 70-SA-0230 [missing 0144, 0148, 0161, 0163, 1070, 0181-0183, 0185, 0187, 0188, 0190, 0192, 0207, 0213, 0222, 0229] (Box 78)
  - 70-SA-0231 through 71-SA-0010 [missing 0240, 0242, 0245, 0266, 0270, 0274, 0276, 0277, 0279, 0284, 0286, 0288-0290, 0295, 0297] (Box 79)
  - 71-SA-0011 through 71-SA-0097 [missing 0044 and 0092. NOTE: Box contains two reports with number SA-71-0042] (Box 80)
  - 72-SA-0001 through 72-SA-0065 (Box 81)
  - 72-SA-0066 through 72-SA-0110 (Box 82)
  - 72-SA-0111 through 72-SA-0180 [missing 0125] (Box 83)
  - 72-SA-0181 through 72-SA-0235 [missing 0208] (Box 84)
  - 72-SA-0246 through 72-SA-0315 (Box 85)
  - 72-SA-0316 through 72-SA-0375 (Box 86)
  - 72-SA-0376 through 72-SA-0430 [missing 0405-0407] (Box 87)
  - 72-SA-0431 through 72-SA-0500 [missing 0462-0467, 0469-0471] (Box 88)
  - 72-SA-0501 through 72-SA-0560 [missing 0543] (Box 89)
  - 72-SA-0561 through 72-SA-0615 [missing 0564] (Box 90)
  - 73-SA-0001 through 73-SA-0085 [missing 0020, 0046, 0049, 0051, 0063, 0067, 0071, 0074] (Box 91)
  - 73-SA-0086 through 73-SA-0140 [missing 0132] (Box 92)
  - 73-SA-0141 through 73-SA-0215 (Box 93)
  - 73-SA-0216 through 73-SA-0290 [missing 0217, 0220, 0258] (Box 94)
  - 73-SA-0291 through 73-SA-0345 [missing 0323] (Box 95)
  - 73-SA-0346 through 73-SA-0390 (Box 96)
  - 73-SA-0391 through 73-SA-0440 (Box 97)
  - 74-SA-0001 through 74-SA-0055 (Box 98)
  - 74-SA-0056 through 74-SA-0130 [missing 0105, 0127] (Box 99)
  - 74-SA-0131 through 74-SA-0180 [missing 0148, 0149] (Box 100)
  - 74-SA-0181 through 74-SA-0245 [missing 0185, 0189, 0198, 0240] (Box 101)
  - 74-SA-0246 through 74-SA-0315 (Box 102)
  - 74-SA-0316 through 74-SA-0375 [missing 0328, 0335, 0340] (Box 103)
  - 74-SA-0376 through 74-SA-0450 [missing 0398, 0420, 0421, 0428] (Box 104)
  - 74-SA-0451 through 74-SA-0510 [missing 0471] (Box 105)
  - 74-SA-0511 through 74-SA-0573 [contained in 7 bound volumes] (Box 106)
  - 74-SA-0574 through 74-SA-0634 [contained in 8 bound volumes] (Box 107)
  - 74-SA-0635 through 74-SA-0681 [contained in 6 bound volumes] (Box 108)
  - 74-SA-0682 through 74-SA-0738 [contained in 6 bound volumes] (Box 109)
  - 74-SA-0739 through 74-SA-0814 [contained in 7 bound volumes] (Box 110)
  - 74-SA- through 74-SA- (Box 111)
  - 74-SA- through 74-SA- (Box 112)
- Reports sorted by year of publication, Series 2
  - 1947, 1948, 1949 (Box 1)
  - 1950, 1951 (Box 2)
  - 1952 Ayer – Worcester plus quarterly and final reports (Box 3)
  - 1953 Ayer – Waterman plus quarterly and final reports (Box 4)
  - 1954 Amo – Worcester plus quarterly and final reports (Box 5)
  - 1955 Boxhall - Mandoli (Box 5)
  - 1955 Manning – Watkins plus quarterly and final reports (Box 6)
  - 1956 Arfin - Maclean (Box 6)
  - 1956 Matthews – Wada plus quarterly and final reports (Box 7)
  - 1957 Arnold – Yabroff plus quarterly and final reports (Box 7)
  - 1958 Abramson - Yhap (Box 8)
  - 1958 Quarterly Status Reports, Abstracts of Unclassified Technical Reports 1949-59, Bibliography of Technical Reports 1949-58 (Box 9)
  - 1959 Anderson - Wightman (Box 9)
  - 1959 Quarterly Status Reports, Bibliography of Technical Reports 1959, Abstracts of Unclassified Technical Reports 1959 (Box 10)
  - 1960 Abramson - May (Box 10)
  - 1960 Merritt – Wilkens plus Data Summaries, Abstracts of Unclassified Technical Reports 1960, Quarterly and Final Status Reports (Box 11)
  - 1961 Achenbach - Patel (Box 12)
  - 1961 Pearson – Yoh plus Quarterly Status Reports, Data Summaries, Final Status Reports (Box 13)
  - 1962 Abramson – Ma (Box 14)
  - 1962 McMurtry - (Box 15)